ICC Lombard shares witness strong rally of 14%
ICC Bank
announced to increase its stake in the company ICC
Bank has announced to increase its stake in the company by 10%. As
part of its plan to buy shares of the company today, ICC
Bank will acquire at least 2.5% of this 10% stake before September 9, 2024.
ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company shares witnessed a
strong rally of up to 14% on Monday.
Currently, the stock
is trading at Rs. 1200.009, up 9.11% on the Seq.
Actually, ICC Bank has announced to increase its 10% stake in the company. As part of its plan to buy shares of the company today, ICC Bank
announced to increase its 10% stake in the company. As part of its
plan to buy shares of the company today, ICC
Bank said in a statement on September 9, 2014
Bank's statement ICC Bank's Board of
Directors has approved an increase of up to 10% in its share holding in
ICC Lombard under Section 192 of the Banking Regulation Act, 1949. The
company said that ICC  Lombard is the
largest company of ICC Bank,
subject to obtaining necessary regulatory approvals. On
March 10, 2023, ICC Lombard had
announced an extension in the time given by the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to reduce ICC Bank's stake in ICC Lombard to less than 30% of the company's paid-up capital by September 9, 2024. As of March 31, 2023, ICC
Bank held
48.00% stake in the company. How has the
performance of shares been? The
performance of shares of ICC Lombard General Insurance Company has
not been very good.
So far this year, the company has
lost more than 100%,
while in the last 1 year, it has declined by 7%.